if you could talk about Tesla a little
bit and what about them well uh free
energy yeah and if he where he got that
information and he downloaded it from
the cosmos and uh and why we weren't
ready for that at the time
well you tell us
it's your world obviously you weren't
ready because your world was operating
still on a lot of fear-based belief
systems
um yeah nevertheless he presented the
opportunity for you to get over that but
your world didn't
and that's still where we're at now
I guess so
now many people are starting to pursue
without fear those ideas again in your
modern times many people are exploring
the idea of how to tap into the
unlimited energy of existence and so
you're getting over your fears and
you're coming back to the place where
you can tap in just as readily as he did
but he gave you an example he gave you a
path he gave you a way to look at things
he is in that sense an inspiration that
allows you to go to that level and
receive what you need to replicate those
ideas
if that's something that excites someone
in your Society
so yes the timing may be more
appropriate now that you might be
letting go of some old style beliefs
that inhibited you before nevertheless
the seed was planted when the seed
needed to be planted
and again sometimes these seeds are
planted to show you
how strongly you might be holding on to
fear-based belief systems how far away
you might be from being in the proper
state to receive the same information
so it's still good information it still
gives you an idea of where you're at
even if you're not ready at that moment
it shows you how not ready you might be
and that gives you something to work
with